What could be worse than having your best friend die?
The Revenant is a comedy, horror, war film directed by D. Kerry Prior.
A horror movie/buddy comedy about Joey and his undead friend Bart who comes back from the dead as a
revenant: an articulate zombie that needs to drink blood to arrest the decomposition of his body.
Joey, played by Chris Wylde.
Bart Gregory, played by David Anders.
Janet, played by Louise Griffiths.
Mathilda, played by Jacy King.
Baily, played by Eric Payne.
Palance, played by Bernardo Badillo.
The Revenant is a 2009 dark comedy/horror film written and directed by
Kerry Prior and starring David Anders and Chris Wylde.
The film was shot in Los Angeles, California.
The film explores themes of police, gangster, vigilante, revenant.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.